http://www.nuffield.ox.ac.uk/the-college/policies-and-resources/page-components/accordion-section/photography/

Home
The College
Policies and Resources
Policies and Resources
Please browse these pages to find information about the policies and procedures which we use to manage our day-to-day activities and fulfill our statutory responsibilities.
Governance
The following documents provide information about Nuffield College governance and legal responsibilities.
Charter, Statutes and By-Laws
List of Trustees
Statement of Accounts (2015-2016)
Statement of Accounts (2014-2015)
Statement of Accounts (2013-2014)
Committee Membership
Charity Registration Certificate
Key Policies
Current written protocols, policies and procedures for delivering our services and responsibilities.
Operational policies and procedures
Anti-Bribery Policy
Code of Practice for External Events
College Statement on Staff-Student Relationships
Complaints Procedure for Students and Staff
Conflict of Interest Policy
Data Protection Policy
Information Security Policy
Freedom of Information
Our Freedom of Information publications scheme follows the standard format required by the Information Commissioner’s Office. Any questions, comments or complaints about the scheme should be sent in writing to the following address:
Information OfficerNuffield College, New Road, Oxford, OX1 1NFE-mail: information.officer@nuffield.ox.ac.uk
Privacy notices and data processing
The following privacy notices and records of processing activities (ROPAs) are currently available.  Date of last update is shown (in brackets).
Applicants for Graduate Study
Privacy Notice (22 October 2018)
ROPA (22 October 2018)
Student data
Privacy Notice (22 October 2018)
ROPA (22 October 2018)
Staff, fellows, associates and academic visitors
Privacy Notice (22 October 2018)
ROPA (22 October 2018)
Information Technology and Library Services
Privacy Notice (22 October 2018)
ROPA (22 October 2018)
Archives
Privacy Notice (29 October 2018)
ROPA (8 April 2020)
Catering, Conferences and Events
Privacy Notice (22 October 2018)
ROPA (22 October 2018)
Access and Security, including CCTV
Privacy Notice (29 October 2018)
ROPA (22 October 2018)
Finance, commercial and related administration
Privacy Notice (22 October 2018)
ROPA (22 October 2018)
Data sharing table
Created 10 October 2018
As anything in the list above is updated (amended) previous versions are preserved.  See our Past privacy notices and ROPAs page for information as to what the processing activities were at points in the past.
Alumni, Donors, and friends
Privacy notice
Photography
When processing photographs including identifiable details, such as people’s faces, the College aims to notify or where possible seek permission from the subject(s). If your image appears on our website and you would like it to be removed, please contact us.
Sometimes, photographs may need to be retained (but not published) as a matter of College record. Please also note that the copyright of photographic images often lies with the photographer, who may be independent of the College.
Find out more about our IT resources.
View more
Find materials and policies relating to finance.
View more
Find policies, procedures, and materials relating to Human Resources. [restricted access]
View more
For policies, procedures, and other documents relevant to students, see our Current Students page.
View more
For further information and materials relating to Fellows, please see the Aide Memoire.  [restricted access]
View more
